字幕校对+特效: 月亮花@MySiLU思路高清
在杨克镇之外，有另一个世界
# Out there There's a world outside of Yonkers #
在那遥远的地方
# Way out there beyond this hick town, Barnaby #
一个美丽的小镇，巴纳比
# There's a slick town, Barnaby #
那里阳光明媚  繁星闪烁
# Out there Full of shine and full of sparkle #
轻合双眸 也能看到它在闪耀，巴纳比
# Close your eyes and see it glisten, Barnaby #
听啊，巴纳比
# Listen, Barnaby #
穿上你的节日盛装 外面的世界才宽广
# Put on your Sunday clothes There's lots of world out there #
甩掉那廉价的发油和雪茄
# Get out the brilliantine and dime cigars #
让我们在晚风中开始探险
# We're gonna find adventure in the evening air #
一袭白衣的女子幽香了夜晚 灯光闪亮如同星辰
# Girls in white in a perfumed night. Where the lights are bright as the stars #
穿上你的节日盛装 我们驶过整座小镇
# Put on your Sunday clothes We're gonna ride through town #
我们乘坐敞篷马车
# In one of those new horsedrawn open cars #
前去观看戴尔莫尼克（大饭店）的表演
# We'll see the shows at Delmonico's #
我们熙熙攘攘，启程回家
# And we'll close the town in a whirl #
我们亲吻心仪的女孩  我们充满青春活力
# And we won't come home until we've kissed a girl #
“Buy N Large加油站”
“Buy N Large银行”
# Buy N Large is your superstore #
“地球被垃圾覆盖 Buy N Large总裁宣称，全球进入紧急状况”
WALL-E帮您摆脱垃圾
您家中垃圾成堆？
Too much garbage in your face?
太空中还空着呢！
There's plenty of space out in space!
BNL星际航班每日出航
BNL star liners leaving each day.
我们将在您外出时 把您家中杂物收拾妥当
We'll clean up the mess while you're away!
BNL舰队中的钻石，Axiom号 （Axiom：真理号）
The jewel of the BNL fleet, the Axiom.
它让您五年的太空之旅豪华舒适
Spend your five-year cruise in style,
全天24小时无间断的周到服务 由全自动的机组人员提供
waited on 24 hours a day by our fully automated crew,
船长和机器人舵手 也将为您呈献无尽的娱乐
while your captain and autopilot
购物，就餐
chart a course for nonstop entertainment, fine dining,
全由畅通无阻的悬浮座椅效劳 连老奶奶都能享受其中乐趣
and with our all-access hoverchairs, even Grandma can join the fun.
您无需步行
There's no need to walk.
Axiom号，星级航班公司的骄傲
The Axiom. Putting the star in executive star liner.
正因为BNL 太空才最终被开拓
Because at BNL, space is the final fun-tier!
…周日… 周日不做周一事…
# No Monday in your Sunday #
周日不穿周一装！
# No Monday in your Sunday clothes #
当你低落时 就请穿上盛装
# Put on your Sunday clothes when you feel down and out #
昂首走上街头 别忘拍照留念
# Strut down the street and have your picture took #
穿得梦幻 精神似乎也已大好
# Dressed like a dream Your spirits seem to turn about #
如果你的气色如周日 那才是真的神采飞扬！
# That Sunday shine is a certain sign. That you feel as fine as you look #
…关于
我们都将忆起…
# And we'll recall #
…当流年似水
# When time runs out #
只要…
# That it only #
…一瞬间
# took a moment #
就被爱上…
# to be loved #
…一生一世！
# a whole life long #
这就是
# And that is all #
爱的真谛
# that love's about #
…一瞬间
#... a moment #
就被爱上…
# To be loved #
…一生一世！
# a whole life long #
“警告 太阳能电量过低”
靠近我，抱紧我
# Hold me close and hold me fast #
你施的魔咒
# The magic spell you cast #
就是玫瑰人生
# This is la vie en rose #
你吻我时，天堂都向我敞开
# When you kiss me heaven sighs #
即使闭上双眼
# And though I close my eyes #
也能看到玫瑰人生
# I see la vie en rose #
当你将我贴近心房
# When you press me to your heart #
我就身处另一个世界
# I'm in a world apart #
那里玫瑰遍地怒放
# A world where roses bloom #
你开口说话 天使便会歌唱
# And when you speak Angels sing from above #
最平凡的语言
# Everyday words seem to #
也成了情歌
#turn into love songs #
取消 （就是不准小WALL-E牵牵小手哦）
方位？数量？你是商贩机器人吗？ （在调查人口哈）
指令？ （是问Wall-E接受何种语言指令）
EVE: Directive?
指令？
嗒嗒~ (以为受到指令去执行预设功能)
WALL-E: Ta-da!
-指…令？ (是你给我的指令吗？) -指令？(这就是你的功能？)
-(ENUNCIATING) Directive? -Directive?
分类完毕！ （知道Wall-E是扫垃圾的了）
Classified.
姓名？ （突然又好奇）
EVE: Name?
Wa…Wall-E
Wall-E？
Wall-E！
Eve
-E… -Eve！
-E…A… -Eve！
-Eve！ -Eva
Eva！
Eve
Eva！ E-E-Eva！
Wall-E…Wall-E！
Eva！
这是我写的一首歌
# Here is a little song I wrote #
一个音符一个音符得唱… 别怕
#... note for note Don't worry #
开心点
# Be happy #
拿着
Here.
看
WALL-E: Look.
爆
Pop.
(你来)啪
You pop.
那就是
# And that is all #
爱的真谛
# that love's about #
我们将忆起…
# And we'll recall #
…当流年似水
# When time runs out #
只要…
# That it only #
…一瞬间
# Took a moment #
就被爱上…
# to be loved #
Eva！
…一生一世
# A whole life long #
Eva？
Eva！
E-E-Eva！
Eva
“外来污染物”
Eva！
Eva
那我们就离开车道 去看场太空虚拟赛车吧
so let's hover over to the driving range and hit a few virtual balls into space.
别，昨天我们已经干过这了 我不想再去
No, we did that yesterday. I don't want to do that.
-那你想干什么呢？ -我也不知道，总得干点什么
-Well, then what do you want to do? -I don't know. Something.
-我们刚卖了… -听着，我已经烦了…
Look, I'm tired of having the same argument over and over.
机器人，这边！
Bot, over here.
[欢迎光临 经济娱乐圈]
-我在隧道里，听不清 -原来你在这儿
-I'm in a tunnel. I can't hear you. -There you are.
[时间12:15 气温22°C]
在Buy N Large 有您快乐所需的一切
Buy N Large. Everything you need to be happy.
您的需求对我们至关重要
Your day is very important to us.
过来！ 拿着，拿着杯子
Hey, drink-bot.
嘿，拿着杯子！
Here, take the cup. Hey, take the cup!
请勿乱动
Please remain stationary.
机器服务员将即刻赶到 为您提供帮助
A service-bot will be here to assist you momentarily.
乘务员！帮帮我！
Stewards! Hello!
请勿乱动！
-Please remain stationary. -Help.
机器服务员将即刻赶到 为您提供帮助
A service-bot will be here to assist you momentarily.
怎么回事？ 发生什么事了？
What's that? What's going on?
Wall-E！
John
-（看到）Eva吗？ -不是，我叫John
Uh, no. John.
Eva！
拜，Wall-E
Bye, WALL-E.
A是Axiom的A 它是你美好的家园
"A" is for Axiom, your home sweet home.
B是Buy N Large的B 它是你生活最好的伙伴
"B" is for Buy N Large, your very best friend.
午餐时间，杯装食品哦
Time for lunch in a cup.
（在这里）体验美丽！
Feel beautiful.
-我在学习呢 -我知道，亲爱的，嘿…
-It's the new you. Stunning. -You look great.
Axiom的消费者请注意！ 试试蓝色，最新时尚哦
Attention, Axiom shoppers. Try blue. It's the new red.
约会？别提约会了，一提我就生气
Date? Don't get me started on the date.
…之前的每一次约会 都完完全全是灾难！
Every holo-date I have been on has been a virtual disaster.
-我只是想找个不那么肤浅的人，你懂吗？ -嗯，我懂，亲爱的
If I could just meet one, one who wasn't so superficial.
世上的男人那么多
There are no good men out there.
嗯，我知道，我知道，因为我… 怎么回…
I know. I know because I've...
Wall-E！
-我叫Mary -Eva！
哦，哦，没问题，过吧
Oh! Oh. Um, sure. You go ahead.
Eva
遮阳伞！
Shade!
我都不知道我们还有游泳池！
I didn't know we had a pool!
船长，有要事，请上驾驶舱
AUTO: Captain, you are needed on the bridge.
我上甲板了！ （可能是梦话）
All hands on deck!
早上好 要打扮打扮吗？
Morning. Just a trim?
哦，我明白 我知道，亲爱的，我知道
I see. I know, honey. I know.
快好了快好了 你看上去棒极了
I'm good, I am good. You look gorgeous.
-船长  -咖啡
-Sir? -Coffee.
船长…
Sir, the annual...
程序，Auto 做事要分主次
Protocol, Auto. First things first.
计算机！状态报告
Computer, status report.
-机械系统？  -正常
-Mechanical systems. -Unchanged.
-反应堆核心温度？  -正常
-Reactor core temperature. -Unchanged.
-乘客人数？  -正常
-Passenger count. -Unchanged.
-食物供应？  -正常
-Regenerative food buffet. -Unchanged.
-太空船维修基地？ -正常
-Jacuzzi pH balance. -Unchanged.
-大气状态？  -正常
-Atmospheric conditions. -Unchanged.
-环境状态？  -正常
-Laundry service volume. -Unchanged.
-好了，Auto -船长，我们有…
-Okay, Auto. -Sir, the annual reconnaissance...
12:30了？Auto，你干嘛不叫醒我 做早晨的例行报告？
-12:30! Auto, why didn't you wake me for morning announcements?
老实说，这恐怕是我在这儿唯一能做的事
Honestly, it's the one thing I get to do on this ship.
各位早上好啊
Well, good morning, everybody,
今天将是你在船上度过的第255，642天
and welcome to day 255,642 aboard the Axiom.
和平时一样，今天气候宜人 温度22摄氏度，阳光普照…
As always, the weather is a balmy 72 degrees and sunny and...
哦，嘿，我看见飞船日志上显示 今天是我们五年巡游的…
Oh, I see the ship's log is showing that today is our 700th anniversary
…700周年纪念日 我相信我们的父辈们…
of our five-year cruise.
…将会很骄傲 因为700多年后的今天…
Well, I'm sure our forefathers would be proud to know that 700 years later
…我们还在做着和当初 他们做的一样的事情
we'd be doing the exact same thing they were doing.
还有，记得下一次用餐要一份免费的…
So, be sure next mealtime to ask for your "free
…“Sep tu a centennial”杯装蛋糕！ 哇，看起来真不错
"septuacentennial cupcake in a cup." Wow, look at that!
同时，今天我们还将…
Also today we have a...
嘿，嘿，Auto，那个按钮 干嘛一直闪？
Hey, Auto, what's that flashing button?
船长，探测机器人Eve带来了好消息
Captain, Probe One has returned positive.
好消息？
Positive?
Eva！
可没有哪个机器人 带回来过好消息…
ever come back positive before.
…从来没有
你好啊船长，恭喜！
Greetings and congratulations, Captain.
如果你看到这个录像，就说明我们的 外太空植物检测仪…
If you are seeing this, that means your Extraterrestrial Vegetation Evaluator,
…也就是EVE探测器已经从地球 带回来一个经确认…
or EVE probe, has returned from Earth
…能进行光合作用的样本
with a confirmed specimen of ongoing photosynthesis.
没错，这就是说，是时候回家了
That's right. It means it's time to go back home.
家？我们回家？
Home? We're going back?
既然地球已经恢复到 生命可以延续的状态…
Now that Earth has been restored to a life-sustaining status,
…嘿，那我们就可以开始 “二次移民计划”了
by golly, we can begin Operation Recolonize.
只要依照手册上的指示，将植物…
Simply follow this manual's instructions
…放入飞船的探测槽
to place the plant in your ship's holo-detector
Axiom将立即自动导航返回地球
and the Axiom will immediately navigate your return to Earth.
这很容易吧！
-It's that easy. -Huh!
不过由于太空的微重力 你和你的乘客可能会…
Now, due to the effects of microgravity,
…出现轻微的骨质疏松
you and your passengers may have suffered some slight bone loss.
不过我相信 只要在飞船的跑步机上稍加锻炼…
But I'm sure a few laps around the ship's jogging track
…你们马上就能恢复正常的体型
will get you back in shape in no time.
我们还有跑步机？
We have a jogging track?
如果你有任何问题 只要参阅手册就好了
If you have any further questions, just consult your operation manual.
等你回家，很快哦！
See you back home real soon.
操作手册
"Operate Manuel."
手册，读出指令！
Manuel, relay instructions.
手册！
Manuel?
哇！瞧瞧这！
Wow. Will you look at that?
瞧瞧
Let's see.
Eva！
Wall-E！
Eva
那就打开看看吧！
Well, let's open her up.
第一步，语音命令 “确认取样”
"Step one. Voice command, 'Confirm acquisition."'
确认取样
-Confirm acquisition.
语音识别以确认权限
Voice authorization required.
额…
-Uh... -CAPTAIN'S VOICE: Uh...
确认
Accepted.
那…那东西在哪？
-Where's the thingy? -Plant.
-植物！  -植物，对，对
Plant. Right. Right.
它在哪？
Where is it?
或许我们漏掉了哪个步骤 重头再看看
Maybe we missed a step.
Wall-E！Wall-E！
-Eva？  -安静！
-EVE? -Plant!
再重新扫描试试，确认一下
Why don't you scan her to be sure?
没有发现样本，探测机器人记忆存储有误
Contains no specimen. Probe's memory is faulty.
-那我们就不回地球了？  -不能
-So then, we're not going to Earth? -Negative.
-那一切又恢复正常了，对吧？  -正确，船长
-I guess things go back to normal, huh? -Correct, Captain.
哦，假警报！
Well, false alarm!
假警报
False alarm.
探测机器人肯定是出故障了
The probe must be defective.
GO-4！把它送去维修部
GO-4, send her to the repair ward,
我要一份她的检测报告 确认下她是不是…
and have them run diagnostics on her. Make sure she's not...
Wall-E！
把Wall-E送去清理？
Have, uh, WALL-E cleaned.
Eva！
分析
Analyze.
分析结果： 外来污染物
Analysis. Foreign contaminant.
此物质由三种基本物质组成…
Substance is a three-phase system
…其中包含多种自然元素的组合
composed of various combinations of naturally derived solids.
分析对象最常用的名称 是soil,dirt,Earth （都有土壤的意思）
Subject is most commonly referred to as soil, dirt, or earth.
Earth？ （土壤，地球）
"Earth"?
解释一下“Earth”
Define "earth."
土地，有别于天空和海洋的星球表面
Earth, the surface of the world as distinct from the sky or sea.
哇！
Wow.
解释“海洋”
Define "sea."
海洋，面积广阔的咸水水域 它们覆盖于绝大多数地球表面
Sea, an expanse of salt water that covers most of the Earth's surface
…并且包围了各大洲
and surrounds its landmasses foreign contaminant.
“外来污染物”
“维修室”
Eva！
打扮一下？打扮一下？ 你看起来好极了！
-Just a trim? -You look gorgeous.
Eve！
安全，安全，安全
Clear, clear, clear.
“诊断”
Eva！
Wall-E！
哦，天啊！
Oh, my.
停下！
Halt!
Wall-E！
警告！危险性机器人
Caution. Rogue robots.
Wall-E！
停下！停下！
Halt! Halt!
警告！危险性机器人
Caution. Rogue robots.
Wall-E！
警告！危险性机器人
Caution. Rogue robots.
Eva！
Eva？
（回）地球
Earth.
地球！
（需要）指令
Directive.
Wall-E
Wall-E！
植物！
Plant!
Wall-E
Eva！
Wall-E！
达到预定航行速度
Cruising speed.
现在可在舱内自由活动
You are now free to move about the cabin.
停下！
20秒后将自爆
Twenty seconds to self-destruct.
10秒后将自爆
Ten seconds to self-destruct.
10，9，8，7，6…
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
5，4，3，2…
six, five, four, three, two
不！不！
(WEAKLY) No. No.
Eva！
Wall-E！
Eve！
-Wall-E -等…等…
Eva
Wall-E！
Wall-E
哦，好多星星啊！
Oh, so many stars.
嘿！嘿，那是… 他叫什么来着？
-Hey! Hey! That's what's-his-name! -Hey! What the...
-嘿，你干什么…  -看呐！看，看！
-Look! Look at that. -Huh? What?
看那儿！
嘿，我知道那小家伙 叫…Wall-E！
Hey. I know that guy. It's, uh, WALL-E.
-就是他！Wall-E！嘿！是我啊，John！ -嗨，Wall-E！
-Hey, WALL-E! It's your buddy John. -Hi, WALL-E!
嗨
Hi.
解释“舞会”
Define "hoedown."
舞会，一种社交场合 人们会在舞会中翩然起舞
Hoedown, a social gathering at which lively dancing would take place.
Auto！真是太神奇了！
Auto, Earth is amazing!
这些东西叫农场！
These are called "farms."
人类把种子种到地里 在上面浇水…
Humans would put seeds in the ground, pour water on them,
…然后食物就长出来了，比如披萨！
and they grow food, like pizza.
晚安，船长
Good night, Captain.
嘿！计算机！
Psst! Computer.
解释“舞蹈”
Define "dancing."
舞蹈，由两个人参与的一系列动作…
Dancing, a series of movements involving two partners
…其速度，节奏与音乐高度和谐
where speed and rhythm match harmoniously with music.
Eva
露天浴场正在关闭
The lido deck is now closing.
-停下！ -你倒是来啊
-JOHN: Stop that. -Make me.
我都不知道我们还有泳池
I didn't know we had a pool.
禁止戏水，禁止潜水
No splashing. No diving.
禁止戏水…禁止…
No splashing. No...
Eva！ （又打开功放“It only takes a moment…”）
（这是）命令！
Directive.
完美的着陆！
Prepare for landing.
我们到了！
"We're here, everybody."
耶，船长！船长，我们到了 真是太美了！
"Yay, Captain! Captain, we're home! It's so beautiful!"
啊，这不算什么 我很乐意为你们服务
"No. It's nothing. I was pleased to do this.
这…这全是为了你们 不是为了我，这…
"It's all about you people. It's not about me."
怎么？
How?
你怎么拿到的？
How did you find it?
我们可以回家了！ 这是头一次！
We can go back home! For the first time!
那儿现在什么样了？
-What's it like now? -Oh!
不，不，不！别告诉我 我要自己看
No, no, no. Don't tell me. I want to see for myself.
等等，这看起来不像是地球啊
Wait. That doesn't look like Earth.
蓝天在哪？
Where's the blue sky?
绿地在哪？
Where's the grass?
当你低落时 就请穿上节日盛装
#... Sunday clothes when you feel down and out #
我听过这首歌
I know that song.
他们在…额…
They're, um,
跳舞，对，跳舞
dancing.Yes, dancing.
你挺过来了，对吧，小家伙？
You made it somehow, huh, little guy?
你没放弃，不是吗？
You didn't give up, did you?
哦，额滴神哪！(呵呵，陕西话)
Okay, then. Come on.
撑住！
Wait a minute.
…当流年似水
#... when time runs out #
只要…
# That it only... #
“启动摄像装置”
Eva？ Eva！
Wall-E
Eva？ Eva
Eva？
Eva
Eva！
来吧，小家伙
There you go, little guy.
你为了喝点水可跑了不少路啊
You came a long way for a drink of water.
得找个人照顾你，那才是…
Just needed someone to look after you, that's...
我们必须回去！
We have to go back.
Auto！下来
Auto, come down here.
是，是，船长
Aye, aye, sir.
Wall-E
Wall-E？
Auto，Eve找到植物了 启动探测槽
Auto, EVE found the plant. Fire up the holo-detector.
没必要，船长 交给我就可以
Not necessary, Captain. You may give it to me.
你猜怎么着？ 我要亲自来
You know what? I should do it myself.
船长！
Captain.
船长，我坚持 把植物给我
Sir, I insist you give me the plant.
Auto，闪开！
Auto, get out of my way.
-你不能回去  -你说什么呢？为什么不行？
-We cannot go home. -What are you talking about? Why not?
那是机密 船长，给我植物
That is classified, Captain. Give me the plant.
什么叫那是机密？ 你不能对船长保密
What do you mean, "classified"? You don't keep a secret from the captain.
-给我植物  -为什么是机密？
-Give me the plant. -Tell me what's classified.
-给我植物  -告诉我，这是命令！
-The plant. -Tell me, Auto! That's an order.
是，船长
Aye, aye, sir.
停下，行吗
Just cut it off, will you?
嘿，你好啊，机器人舵手 我有些坏消息
Hey, there, autopilots. Got some bad news.
清洁行动…失败了
Operation Cleanup has, well, failed.
有毒物质的含量不断升高 地球已经不适合生命的生存
Wouldn't you know, rising toxicity levels have made life unsustainable on Earth.
不适合生存？什么？
"Unsustainable"? What?
恐怕我要取消“二次移民计划”了…
Darn it all, we're going to have to cancel Operation Recolonize.
…所以呆在那，嗯… 别想着解决这问题了…
So,Just stay the course.Rather than try and fix this problem,
…或许大家都呆在太空中更容易些
it'll just be easier for everyone to remain in space.
容易？
"Easier"?
-总裁先生…总裁先生  -但我以为…嗯？
-Mr. President? -I think...
-该走了！  -好，我现在下发…
-Huh? -Sir, time to go.
…A113号优先执行命令 机器人舵手有权…
Okay. I'm giving Override Directive A 113.
…掌管飞船一切事宜 不要回地球
Go to full autopilot. Take control of everything, and do not return to Earth.
重复一遍，不要回地球！
Repeat, do not return to Earth.
赶紧离开这鬼地方
Let's get the heck out of here.
现在，给我植物
Now, the plant.
不！等会！
No. Wait a minute.
计算机，那则信息 是什么时候发到Axiom的？
Computer, when was that message sent out to the Axiom?
此信息于2110年收到
Message received in the year 2110.
那…那差不多是700年前了！
That's... That's nearly 700 years ago!
Auto，情况都变了！ 我们一定要回去！
Auto, things have changed! We've got to go back.
船长，命令是 “不要回到地球”
Sir, orders are "do not return to Earth."
但生命已经可以生存了
But life is sustainable now.
瞧瞧这株植物！ 这么绿，这么旺盛
Look at this plant. Green and growing.
这是活生生的证据，他错了！
It's living proof he was wrong.
-无关，船长  -这完全有关！
-Irrelevant, Captain. -What? It's completely relevant!
我们的家在那儿 家，Auto！而它现在正需要帮助
Out there is our home.Home, Auto. And it's in trouble.
我不能就这么坐着无所事事
I can't just sit here and do nothing.
我一直以来干得就是这种事！
That's all I've ever done.
那也是这艘该死的飞船上所有人干得事！
That's all anyone on this blasted ship has ever done.
那就是无所事事！
Nothing!
只有在Axiom你才能生存
On the Axiom you will survive.
我不想“生存”！ 我想“生活”！
I don't want to survive. I want to live!
请听从我的指示
Must follow my directive.
我才是Axiom的船长 我们今天就回家！
I'm the captain of the Axiom. We are going home today.
GO-4？嘿！
GO-4? Hey! That's not...
简直是造反！ Eve，抓住他！
This is mutiny! EVE, arrest him.
Eve，你要把这株植物直接放进探测槽
EVE, you are to put this plant straight in the holo-detector.
不！
No!
Eva？
-Wall-E！ -Wall-E！
Eva！
-扔过来！把它扔过来！  -Wall-E！
Over here. Throw it.
Eva！
把植物交给我
Give me the plant.
不！
Wall-E！
禁止一切通讯
All communications are terminated.
-你将被软禁在寓所  -不！
You are confined to quarters.
造反了！造反了！
No! Mutiny! Mutiny!
“重启”
Wall-E？
注意！密封舱启动 以进行废物处理
Caution. Activating airlock disposal.
Wall-E！
密封舱开启 进行废物处理
Activating airlock disposal.
Wall-E！
-Eve…  -Wall-E！
注意！密封舱开启 进行废物处理
Caution. Activating airlock disposal.
密封舱开启 进行废物处理
Activating airlock disposal.
Wall-E！
Eve…
Wall-E
M-O
-M-O？  -M-O
（这是）指令
Directive.
（这才是）指令
（回）地球
Earth.
地球！
地球？
Earth.
地球
地球？地球！
Earth? Earth!
-M-O  -Wall-E！
错误
Wrong.
请保持冷静 我们正在…
Please hold. We are currently having...
Eva！
警告！危险性机器人
Caution. Rogue robots.
这造型挺适合你
That style suits you.
警告！危险性机器人
Caution. Rogue robots.
不可能！
Not possible.
警告！危险性机器人
Caution. Rogue robots.
Auto！Auto！听见我了吗？
Auto! Auto! Mutiny. Mutiny.
你个白痴方向盘
Stupid wheel.
警告！危险性机器人
Caution. Rogue robots.
植物！
The plant!
哈，看看现在是谁该傻眼了！
We'll see who's powerless now.
喂，喂，通了吗？
Testing, testing. Is this thing on?
嘿，我是船长，我现在被关起来了
This is the captain. I am locked in my room.
Eve，Wall-E，把那植物带到露天浴场去
EVE, WALL-E, bring the plant to the lido deck.
回去启动探测槽
I'll have activated the holo-detector. Now, hurry.
快！Auto可能正在掐线…
Auto's probably going to cut me off...
停下！
Halt.
哦，天！
Oh, my.
安全！ （这个秀逗机器人只会说这一句话）
Clear.
停下！停下！
Halt, halt.
-瞧瞧我拿到什么了，Auto！  -不可能
-Look what I got, Auto. -Not possible.
没错！植物哦
That's right. The plant.
哦，你想要吗？ 想要就放马过来啊，傻冒
You want it? Come and get it, blinky.
不！
No.
船长？船长？
Captain? Captain?
放开！
Let go.
-放开！  -拉不动我吗？
-Let go. -Too heavy for you? Huh?
只要我还活着就休想躲过我…
You're not getting away from me, one-eye.
-放手  -你就这么点水平？
-Get off. -Is that all you got?
走开！
停下！
Halt.
-我坚持，这不好  -靠近点啊，成了！
-That's it. A little closer. -Cease and desist. -Not good. -Got you.
保持冷静！ 保持冷静！
Remain calm. Remain calm.
女士们先生们 现在在说话的是你们的船长
Ladies and gentlemen, this is your captain speaking.
我们这的机器舵手 出了点小问题
We're having a slight malfunction with the autopilot.
请，保持冷静
Please remain calm.
够了
Enough.
-抓着！  -不！不，不！
-抓着我！  -救命！
拉住你了！
I gotcha!
John，准备好接宝宝！
John, get ready to have some kids!
小心！
Look out!
不！
No.
Wall-E！
不！
Oh, no!
Wall-E！
Auto！
Auto，你被“炒鱿鱼”了！
Auto, you are relieved of duty.
不…
No.
植物！植物！
Plant! Plant!
-植物！ -Eva！
-Plant! -EVE!
植物来源分析
Plant origin verified.
Wall-E
前往地球 航线调整中
Course set for Earth.
十秒之后开始空间跳跃 （类似时空穿梭）
Ten seconds to hyper-jump. Nine...
-9，8，7，6，5… -不，Wall-E！
eight...seven, six, five, four...
哦，别，Wall-E…
Oh, no. WALL-E.
4，3，2，1，0
...three, two, one, zero.
Wall-E！
Eva！
“太阳能充电等级”
Wall-E
Eve
Wall-E？
当你情绪低落时 就穿上节日盛装
# Put on your Sunday clothes when you feel down and out #
Wall-E？
Wall-E，我们到家了！
Wall-E！ Wall-E！
-Eva？  -Wall-E？
Eva？
那就是…
# And that is all #
…爱的真谛
# That love's about #
-耶！-好诶！ -去，去，去！
Go, go, go. Go, go.
…当流年似水
# And we'll recall When time runs out #
这叫“种田”
This is called farming!
你们可以种各种各样的植物！
You kids are going to grow all kinds of plants.
长蔬菜的，长披萨的…
Vegetable plants. Pizza plants!
回家真好！
It's good to be home!
…一瞬间
# Took a moment #
就被爱上…
# to be loved #
…一生一世！
# a whole life long #
你知道你的双脚被系住
# Did you think that your feet had been bound #
被什么引力拉至地表？
# By what gravity brings to the ground? #
你觉得被自己选择的未来所迷惑吗？
# Did you feel you were tricked by the future you picked? #
那么，下来吧
# Well, come on down #
所有的自然规律在高空都不适用
# All these rules don't apply When you're high in the sky #
所以，下来吧
# So come on down #
下来吧
# Come on down #
你下到地面
# We're coming down to the ground #
没有比这儿更好的地方
# There's no better place to go #
我们上有山雪
# We got snow up on the mountains #
我们下有河川
# We got rivers down below #
我们要下到地面
# We're coming down to the ground #
我们听到树梢的鸟语
# We hear the birds sing in the trees #
大地将被呵护
# And the land will be looked after #
我们在微风中播撒种子
# We'll send the seeds out in the breeze #
你觉得逃脱了世俗
# Did you think you'd escaped from routine #
用改变剧本与场景的方法？
# By changing the script and the scene? #
不管你是什么样的人
# Despite all you made of it #
你总是害怕改变
# You're always afraid of the change #
其实你内心很有胆识
# You've got a lot on your chest #
就来当我的客人吧
# Well, you can come as my guest #
那么，下来吧
# So come on down #
下来吧
# Come on down #
我们将下到地面
# We're coming down to the ground #
没有比这儿更好的地方
# There's no better place to go #
我们上有山雪
# We got snow up on the mountains #
我们下有河川
# We got rivers down below #
我们要下到地面
# We're coming down to the ground #
我们听到树梢的鸟语
# We hear the birds sing in the trees #
大地将被呵护
# And the land will be looked after #
我们在微风中播撒种子
# We'll send the seeds out in the breeze #
就像海里的鱼儿
# Like the fish in the ocean #
海也是我们的家
# We felt at home in the sea #
我们学习在美好的土地上生活
# We learned to live off the good land #
我们学习爬树
# We learned to climb up a tree #
我们双腿站着成长
# Then we got up on two legs #
但我们还想飞
# But we wanted to fly #
当我们把家弄乱了
# And when we messed up our homeland #
却远走高飞
# We set sail for the sky #
我们要下到地面
# We're coming down to the ground #
没有比这儿更好的地方
# There's no better place to go #
我们上有山雪
# We got snow up on the mountains #
我们下有河川
# We got rivers down below #
我们要下到地面
# We're coming down to the ground #
我们听到树梢的鸟语
# We hear the birds sing in the trees #
大地将被呵护
# And the land will be looked after #
我们在微风中播撒种子
# We'll send the seeds out in the breeze #
我们要下来
# We're coming down #
下到地球上
# Coming down to Earth #
就像出生的婴儿
# Like babies at birth #
来到这世界
# Coming down to Earth #
我们知是非和轻重
# We define new priorities #
这些是优点和美德
# These are extraordinary qualities #
我们要下到地面
# We're coming down to the ground #
没有比这儿更好的地方
# There's no better place to go #
我们上有山雪
# We got snow up on the mountains #
我们下有河川
# We got rivers down below #
我们要下到地面
# We're coming down to the ground #
我们听到树梢的鸟语#
# We hear the birds sing in the trees #
大地将被呵护
# And the land will be looked after #
我们在微风中播撒种子
# We send the seeds out in the breeze #
我们要下到地面
# We're coming down to the ground #
没有比这儿更好的地方
# There's no better place to go #
我们上有山雪
# We got snow up on the mountains #
我们下有河川
# We got rivers down below #
我们要下到地面
# We're coming down to the ground #
我们听到树梢的鸟语
# We hear the birds sing in the trees #
大地将被呵护
# And the land will be looked after #
我们在微风中播撒种子
# We send the seeds out in the breeze #
我们知是非和轻重
# We define new priorities #
这些是优点和美德
# These are extraordinary qualities #
能在地球上找到
# To find on Earth #